前情提要：
Previously on Friends:
-工作的事怎么样？ -他给了我一份工作。
- How did the job stuff go? - He offered me one!
这时候该来一瓶以色列的佳酿。
You know what? This calls for a bottle of lsrael's finest!
工作是在巴黎。
The job is in Paris.
天啊，你们说话呀。
Oh,God,please,somebody say something.
如果你接受这份工作 你将要搬去巴黎吗？
So if you take this job,you'll be moving to Paris?
难道是乘飞机上下班？
Or facing a bitch of a commute.
我明白这很艰巨，我感到恐惧 而且离你们那么那么的遥远。
I know,it's huge,and it's scary and it's really far away from you guys.
可是这对我是一个很好的机会。
But this is such an incredible opportunity for me.
我还跟他们说明了艾玛的情况
I've already told them about our situation with Emma..
他们答应尽力给予我方便。
and they said they'll do whatever we need to make us feel comfortable.
我可以回来看望她，你也可以带她去看望我。 满足我们任何要求。
I mean,I'll fly back and forth,they'll fly you out. Anything we want.
我老板答应给我的睡房买一盏新的台灯。
My boss said I might be getting a new lamp in my cubicle.
- 好的，没问题。 - 谢谢。
- All right. We'll work it out. - Oh,thank you. Thank you.
-这是你渴望的吗？ -我相信是。
- You sure this is what you want? - I think it is.
-怎么了？ -我得到一份很棒的工作。
- What's going on? - I got a really incredible job offer.
- 太好了。 - 为你高兴。
- Hey,great! All right! - Good for you!
-是在巴黎。 -什么？
- It's in Paris. - What?
不…不…不… 发生太多改变了
No,no,no! No,no,no! No,too much is changing,okay?
首先，菲比结婚了 …恭喜。
First Phoebe getting married. Congratulations.
然后这两个家伙要搬到，那所讨厌的房子。
And then these two move in to a stupid house in the stupid suburbs.
-嘿，今天下午你还说会支持的。 -我变来变去的，不能相信我。
- Earlier,you said you'd be supportive. - It comes and goes. I wouldn't trust it!
伙计们,这对我十分十分重要。
You guys,this is really,really important to me.
如果你们尝试接受，我会很感激的。
It means a lot if you could try to get onboard.
-我们当然会。恭喜你。 - 谢谢
- Of course we can. Congratulations. - Thank you.
乔伊
Joey?
我只关心留在美国的那些人。
No,my hugs are reserved for people staying in America!
乔伊，我…
Joey,it would mean..
不，要去法国的人别靠近我。
No! Get your France-going arms away from me!
-你不会难过吗？ -实际上我感到伤心。
- Are you okay with this? - Well,it makes me feel sad,but..
- 我是在问罗斯 - 知道了。
- Talking to Ross. - I see.
瑞秋去了另一个国家 不能每天看到她？
Rachel moving to another country? Not being able to see her every day?
我怎么会不难过！？
How could I be okay with this?
我们又能怎么样？她需要这份工作。
But what are we gonna do? She really needs this job.
如果罗夫罗兰公司请她回去，她会愿意吗？
Do you think if Ralph Lauren offered her her old job back,she would take it?
这怎么可能？
How's that gonna happen?
你就是这么使用你的3个魔法愿望的吗？
Is this the best way to use one of your three magic wishes?
也许，我能跟她的老板谈谈。
Like,I don't know,I could talk to her boss. Yeah.
对，我跟他在圣诞派对见过面。 我们相处的很好。
I met him at that Christmas party. I mean,we really hit it off.
-是那个一直管你叫罗的家伙吗？ -我并没有说我们是兄弟呀。
- The guy who kept calling you "Ron"? - I didn't say we were brothers!
技术上说,这不算拥抱
Technically,this is not a hug.
艾斯黛去世
The.One.Where.Estelle.Dies
你在读讣告?
You read the obituaries?
是的,而且,我受到一些人的诅咒
Yeah. Well,I got a few curses on people.
我只想看看他们有什么下场
I just like to see how they're coming.
- 嘿，菲比 - 嘿。
- Hey,Phoebe. Hey. - Hi.
在我们打算买的那座房子旁边， 有一座房子也在出售。
The house next door to the one that we're buying just went on the market.
我想去看看，可钱德不愿意。
I wanna take a look at it,but Chandler doesn't.
我们明天就签约了。
We close escrow tomorrow.
再看其它房子只会迷惑自己。 我们很容易感到迷惑
Seeing another house can only confuse us. We're easily confused.
我们并不机灵。
We're not very bright.
那如果它比我们的更好呢 至少应该看看。
But what if it's better than ours? Shouldn't we look?
你怎么看，菲比？
What do you think,Phoebe?
我觉得你穿这件衬衣 像巴斯金罗宾斯雪糕餐厅的服务员。
Well,I think that shirt makes you look like you should work at a Baskin-Robbins.
反正怎么都像。
Anyway..
- 乔伊的经纪人是艾斯黛雷纳多吗？ - 对.
- Hey,isn't Joey's agent Estelle Leonard? - Yeah.
- 她死了。 - 真的吗？
- She died. - You're kidding!
- 真糟糕。 -是的，在上个星期。
- That's terrible. - Yeah,last Saturday.
哇！她是第一个独自驾机飞越大西洋的黑人男性。
Wow! She was the first black man to fly solo across the Atlantic!
-哦，等等。我看错了另一个。 -哦？
- Wait a minute,I read the wrong one. - Oh,yeah?
-她只是一个经济人。 -乔伊肯定感到很难过。
- Yeah,she was just an agent. - Joey's gonna be so upset.
是的。他一直希望成为第一个独自驾机飞越大西洋的黑人男性。
I know. He always wanted to be the first black man to cross the Atlantic.
我们不能让乔伊知道这件事。
We cannot tell Joey about this.
一切都在改变，他都快要发疯了。
He's already flipping out about everything changing.
不能再刺激他了。
This'll push him over the edge.
-你真的认为我们不应该告诉他吗？ -至少暂时不说。
- You don't think we should tell him? - Not for a while.
给他几天，先消化已经发生了的事。
Let's just give him a few days to get used to everything else.
如果他从报纸上看到呢？
What if he reads the paper?
除非是八卦的史努比告诉查理布朗 否则就没问题。
Unless Snoopy says it to Charlie Brown,I think we're okay.
-有什么事吗？ -我是瑞秋格林的朋友。
- May I help you? - Yeah. I'm a friend of Rachel Green's.
我们2年前在圣诞派对上见过面。
Actually,we met at the Christmas party about two years ago.
- 哦，是唐吗？ - 差不多，是罗。
- Oh,right. Don? - Close. Ron.
有什么能帮忙的吗？
Well,what can I do for you?
想了解一下，能不能恢复瑞秋的工作？
Well,I'm here to see if you'll give Rachel her job back.
是她让你来的吗？
Did she ask you to come here and do this?
不。如果你同意了
First I have to get you to agree..
我还要问问她是否愿意回来。
then we'll see if she wants to come back.
哇，这真吸引人。
Wow,that is tempting.
她很喜欢这份工作 实际上你找不到比她更好的人选
She loved her job here. Let's face it,you're not gonna find anyone..
是这样吗？
who did it as well as she did. Isn't that true?
-是很不错。 - 我真没料到。
- She is good. - I took a shot there.
可是，很抱歉。我无能为力。
But I'm sorry,there's nothing I can do.
事实是，我不想出力。
Oh,that's not true. There's nothing I want to do.
好的。
I see.
谢谢
Thanks very much.
-是你儿子吗？ -对，他叫罗斯。
- Is this your son? - Yeah,his name is Ross.
-怎么了？ - 没什么，跟罗很接近嘛。
- What? - Nothing,it's just that it's close to Ron.
这小罗斯也会碰巧对恐龙有兴趣吗？
Does little Ross like dinosaurs,by any chance?
是的，他老是说起。那又怎么样？
Yeah,they're all he talks about. Why?
他是否愿意和我到自然历史博物馆
How would he like to come with me to the Museum of Natural History..
在其他人都离开之后，就剩我们两个。
after everyone else has left,just the two of us..
他想摸哪里就摸哪里。
and he can touch anything he wants?
我说的，你都听到了。 不是那么回事。
I just heard it how you must have heard it,and that's not good.
让我再说一遍。 我是古生物学家。
Let me start again. I'm a paleontologist.
你也可以在场 摸的只会是骨头……和化石。
You'll be there with us,and the touching refers only to bones.. fossils!
-你真的可以安排到吗？ -如果你能让瑞秋回来，那就这么定了。
- You could really arrange that? - You let Rachel come back and it's done.
我想，让瑞秋回来，不见得就是坏事。
I guess having Rachel back wouldn't be the worst thing in the world.
太好了，十分感谢。
Yes! Thank you! This is great! Thank you so much.
我保证，这是你的孩子终身难忘的经历。
I swear,your kid's gonna have the time of his life.
太好了。我对他挺担心的。
That's great. I worry about little Ross.
他老是捧着书本，收集石头。 完全被恐龙给迷住了。
He's always reading,collecting rocks and he's obsessed with dinosaurs.
他会很好的。
He'll be fine!
- 嘿，菲比。 - 嘿。
- Hey,Phoebe. - Hey.
-你怎么了？ -我在生我经纪人的气。
- Everything okay? - I'm just mad at my agent.
艾斯黛？为什么？
Estelle? Why?
有一部电视电影 其中的角色很合适我演。
There's a part in this TV movie that I would be perfect for..
她没有推荐我去。她必须告诉我原因。
and I didn't even get put up for it. She better have a good reason.
我想她有原因的。
I'm guessing she does.
我想听听，她老是这样。
Well,I wanna hear it,because she keeps doing this.
噢，等等。我要先走了。
No,wait,wait,wait! All right,I gotta go.
答应我，等一会再打给她。
Just listen. Promise me that you will wait a minute before you call her.
为什么？
Well,okay. Why?
因为，朋友之间的诺言，从不需要有原因。
Because a promise between friends means never having to give a reason.
我喜欢这句话。
I love that saying!
-嗨！ - 乔伊，我是艾斯黛。
- Hello? - Joey,it's Estelle.
我正想打电话给你。太怪了。
I was just gonna call you. That's weird.
这是巧合，但是可信。
It's a little coincidental,but believable.
我想你肯定想知道，我为什么没有安排你
Listen,I'm sure you're wondering why I didn't get you..
为那部电视电影试镜。
an audition for that TV movie.
是的，确实是的。
Yeah,actually I am.
我想我失职了。哦！
I guess I dropped the ball there.
就这样？似乎你最近老是失职。
That's it? You know,it seems like all you do lately is drop the ball.
不要这么和我说话。你以为自己是谁？
Don't take that tone with me. Who do you think you are?
阿兰・莱蒙？ 第一个独自驾机飞越大西洋的黑人男性？
Alan Lemon,the first black man to fly solo across the Atlantic?
听我说，你是我的经纪人。
No,look,all I'm saying is you're my agent..
但是你没有为我争取到试镜机会。 我受够了。
and you're not getting me any auditions and I'm tired of it.
你这样说什么意思？
What are you saying?
我意思是，不能再这样了。 艾斯黛
I'm saying that this isn't working for me anymore,okay,Estelle?
你被解雇了。再见。
You're fired. Goodbye.
噢，这个星期艾斯黛真不走运。
Man,tough week for Estelle.
- 嗨。 - 嗨。
- Hi. - Hi.
艾玛把这忘在我房间了。
Emma left her stuffed T. rex at my house.
-没这个她可睡不着哦。 -嗯，她现在在睡觉呢。
- You know she can't sleep without it. - Well,she's asleep now.
-别再塞这玩意儿给她。 - 好的。
- Stop forcing that thing on her. - Okay.
哦，你绝对不会相信今天发生的事。
You're not gonna believe what happened to me today!
罗夫罗兰公司打电话请我回去。
Ralph Lauren called and gave me my job back!
-不会吧。 -这是多么古怪呀。
- No! - I mean,it was the weirdest thing.
他们先是解雇我 然后又无缘无故重新聘用我。
They fire me and then out of nowhere,they just hire me back.
一定是没我就不行了。
I mean,that place must just be falling apart without me!
-那么，你不去巴黎了吧。 -去呀。我还去。
- So you're not going to Paris? - No,I'm still going!
什…什么？！
What?
好吧,当路易斯威登公司发现
Well,when the Louis Vuitton people found out..
罗夫罗兰公司请我回去 他们就提高了我的报酬。
that Ralph Lauren wanted me back,they offered me more money!
罗斯,是不是太棒了？
Ross,isn't that great?
我们有意买下旁边的那座房子。 允许我们参观一下这里吗？
Hi. We're buying the house next door. Could we just take a look around?
当然可以。 我刚好带人来参观，你们进来吧。
Sure,I'm showing it to someone else right now,but please,look around.
我感到这是对我们房子的不忠。
I feel like we're cheating on our house.
你会为了另一座年轻漂亮的房子
If we cheat,shouldn't it be with a hot,younger house..
而对老房子不忠吗？
that does stuff that our house won't do?
我们的比这里更棒。
Ours is so much better!
客厅更小。餐厅像个洞穴。
This living room is smaller,the dining room looks like a cave.
真受不了。
What a hole!
-你们觉得怎么样？ -喜欢!
- So,what do you think? - Love it!
我们本来有一位买家 楼上的女士是另一位。
We already have one offer. I think the lady upstairs will make another one.
是我们的邻居耶。他们是什么样的？
They could be our neighbors. What are they like?
楼上这位女士很好，她和丈夫有2个小孩。
The woman upstairs is nice. She and her husband have two kids.
-丈夫在华尔街工作，她是… -喔…我的…上帝啊
- He's on Wall Street,and she's a.. - Oh.. my.. God!
没错。
Sure.
乔伊，你想和我去…？
Hey,Joey,you wanna come with me to..?
你怎么啦？
Are you okay?
我为解雇艾斯黛的事难过。
Yeah,I just feel bad about firing Estelle.
她肯定伤心死了。
This has gotta be killing her.
她不会因此死的。
No,that wouldn't kill her.
除非她有血栓塞。
A coronary embolism might.
她肯定很难过。我是她唯一的客户
I don't know. She's gotta be taking it hard. I was her only client.
那个会吃纸的家伙除外。
Except for this guy who eats paper.
我猜他吃的钱比挣得多。
And I'm guessing he eats more money than he makes.
我明白她不是优秀的经纪人， 但我们合作10年了。
Look,I know she's not a great agent,but she did stick with me for 10 years.
-我要给她打电话，重新雇佣她。 -不…不…不要给她打电话，
- I'm gonna call her and hire her again. - No,no,no! Don't call her.
-你等她给你打电话。 - 为什么？
- You wait for her to call you. - Why?
耐心是通向理解的大道
Because patience is the road to understanding.
那是得到快乐的关键。
Which is the key to a happy heart.
你真让人吃惊，我服了。
You blow me away.
答应我，你等她给你打电话。
All right,so promise you're gonna wait for her to call you?
-我答应你。 - 好的
- I promise. - Okay.
这意味着，从不需要有原因。
And that means never having to give a reason.
这世界真小呀。
What a small world!
我还没碰到过碧昂丝（流行天后）
And yet I never run into Beyonce.
你们认识？
You two know each other?
在莫妮卡认识他之前
We go way back. Before Monica made an honest man out of him..
钱德是我的小甜饼。
Chandler used to be my little love muffin.
别审我
Don't judge me.
为什么不?我要.
Why not? I do.
这么说，你们也要想买下一座房子。
So are you guys thinking of getting this house too?
如果是要投标竞价的话 我可要警告你了 我可是流氓
Are we gonna have a bidding war? I better warn you,I'm a toughie.
哦不
Don't.. Don't.. Don't..
不要
Don't do that.
其实我打算买下隔壁那座房子。
No,actually,we are buying the house next door.
为...为什么？
Why?
我不知道为什么
I don't know why.
那就这么定了。 本来我还在犹豫。
Oh,that decides it,then! I was on the fence.
没想到我们会成为邻居。
But knowing that you two would be our neighbors?
那我就买下来了。
Now we have to get it!
艾伦，我们去定下价钱。
Ellen,we're gonna talk numbers.
怎么会搞成这样？
This cannot be happening.
经纪人不是说还有 另外一对夫妇有意购买吗？
The realtor said another couple made an offer.
珍妮丝可能就买不成了。 另外的夫妇可能会买下。
Maybe the Janices won't get it! Maybe the other couple will.
这绝不可能发生 除非那是希特勒夫妇才能抢过她。
The only way that'll happen is if the other couple are the Hitlers!
我们两座房子都买下来，怎么样？
Okay,okay! All right,what if we get both houses?
-将这里作为家庭旅馆。 -真是好主意。
- We can turn this one into a guesthouse! - That's a great idea!
不过我想知道
By the way,I don't mean to sound distasteful..
你从什么时候开始爱乱花钱了。
but when did you start crapping money?
-好呀。那你来想办法。 - 好啊
- You come up with an idea. - All right.
还有3个小时才签约
We've still got three hours till escrow closes on our house.
-我们现在取消还来得及。 -我们喜欢这座房子。
- We can still get out. - But we love our house.
你也同样喜欢住在她隔壁吗？
Will we love it so much with her next door?
她还会在这大声嚷嚷，
And she's gonna be louder out here too!
讨厌的“喔…我的…上帝呀…”
Just the crickets and,"Oh.. my.. God!"
即使我们不买这座房子 她还是会在我们面前出现。
Okay. But if we don't get this house,she'll still show up wherever we go.
她住在这，起码不会突然吓我们一跳。
At least if she's here,it eliminates the element of surprise.
你不会再听到那3个字
Never again will you have to hear the three words..
连你的蛋蛋都被吓得缩进去。
that make your balls jump back up inside your body!
我们得想想办法 不能就让她住在隔壁。
Well,we have to do something. We can't have her living next door.
嗯，确实会。
Oh,that does it too.
谁？
Who is it?
是我，罗。
It's me. Ron.
我知道瑞秋拒绝你了。
Look,I know Rachel turned you down..
不过我有一个法子能让她回来。
but I think there's a way you might be able to get her to come back.
请你别见怪，重新聘用已经解雇的员工 不是我主要的工作。
This may surprise you,but rehiring fired employees is not my main job.
先听我说。
Just hear me out.
给她提高薪酬，你认为怎么样？
How would you feel about offering her a raise?
不好。罗。
Not good,Ron.
可能我会说服你。
Perhaps I can persuade you.
你希望送给你儿子
What if you could give your son..
这么一只恐龙蛋吗？
this genuine pterodactyl egg replica.
哇，这很不错呀。
Wow! That's pretty cool.
这么说…我们成交了？
So? Do we have a deal?
-好的。你成功了。 -太好了！
- Okay,you got it. - Yes! Yes!
这会让我很受欢迎。
This is gonna make me very popular.
喔，相信我，女士都喜欢。
Believe me,the ladies,they love it.
我指的是我儿子。
I meant with my son.
对。女士对它不感兴趣。
Good,because the ladies,not so much.
乔伊，我是艾尔， 那个吃纸的人。
Joey,this is Al Zebooker,the guy who eats paper.
相信你听说了艾斯黛过世的消息。
I'm sure you've heard that Estelle passed away.
我通知你参加追悼会
I wanted to let you know there 's a memorial for her..
在韦斯特赛德教堂，明天10点。
at the Westside Chapel tomorrow at 10.
希望你能来。
Hope you can make it.
天呀。
Oh,my God.
-你好? - 乔伊，我是艾斯黛。
- Hello? - Joey,it' s Estelle.
艾斯黛？
Estelle?
我打电话是要告诉你 我没有因为你解雇我而感到伤心。
Yeah,I wanted to call and tell you that there's no hard feelings for firing me.
好的。真难以置信你会打电话给我。
Okay. I just.. I can't believe you're calling me.
我觉得我不应该冒然造访。
I didn't think I should just drop by.
不，不要来访。
No,no! Don't drop by! Don't drop by!
总之，你继续做你的事。我很好。
Anyway,you did what you had to do. I'm okay.
能问你个问题吗？
Can I ask you something?
你那边怎么样？
What's it like there?
还凑合。
It's all right.
我要挂了。祝你好运
Look,kiddo,I gotta go.
你会飞黄腾达的。
Good luck with the career. You're gonna be huge!
谢谢你艾斯黛。再见。
Thanks for everything,Estelle. Bye.
不在服务区？！我说呢。
"Out of area." Boy,I'll say!
我们讨论过了。
Well,I just talked to Sid.
我们要买下这座房子
We are definitely putting in an offer on the house.
一定会成功的。
And I'll bet we get it!
希特勒夫妇肯定会很失望。
The Hitlers will be so disappointed.
我要先走了。帮我跟莫妮卡说再见。
All right,I gotta run. Tell Monica I say goodbye.
我们回头见，邻居。
I'll see you later,neighbor.
等等。
Wait!
我想告诉你。 你住在这里我很开心。
I just want you to know that I'm so happy you're going to be here.
噢，我也是。
Oh,me too!
因为
Because..
这样…
that way..
我们就能再续前缘。
we can pick up where we left off.
我一直都爱着你。
I never stopped loving you.
-喔…我的… -对对。
- Oh.. my.. - Yeah,yeah,yeah,yeah.
我想你
I want you.
我爱你
I need you.
我要你，珍妮丝・利特曼・高软尼克・尼・豪森斯特
I must have you,Janice Litman-Goralnik nee Hosenstein.
钱德，你在说什么啊？
Chandler,what are you talking about?
你现在住在隔壁，我们会每天在一起。
Now that you live next door,we can be together every day.
莫妮卡根本不会察觉。
Sid and Monica never have to know a thing.
我不知道该说什么。
I don't know what to say.
很显然，我们之间还有热情。
I mean,you know,obviously we have this heat between us.
很显然。
Obviously.
但我爱我的丈夫。
But I love my husband.
我也知道你爱你的妻子。
And I know you love your wife.
我现在认为我不应该买这座房子。
I don't think we should get this house now.
别这么说，别打破我们的美梦。
Don't say that. Don't dangle the dream and take it away.
钱德 我们其中必须有一个人立场要坚定。
Chandler,one of us has got to be strong.
我知道。
I understand.
尽管…，
Although..
最后就软弱一次吧。
Maybe just one last moment of weakness.
再见了，钱德宾
Goodbye,Chandler Bing.
我的蛋蛋不会再缩回去了。
They're never coming down now!
-嘿。 -嘿。
- Hi. - Hi!
嘿，你肯定不会相信今天的事。
You are never going to believe what happened to me today.
是什么？
What?
罗夫罗兰公司又打电话来了。 而且他们给我更高的报酬。
Ralph Lauren called,again,and they offered me more money.
- 真的吗？ - 是的。
- They did? - Yes!
真的太古怪了。 则纳说愿意以任何代价请我回去。
It was the weirdest thing.Zelner called me and said,"We will do anything we can to get you back."
还说我应该为此感谢罗。
And that I should thank some "Ron."
可我连他是谁都不知道。
I don't even know what department that guy's in!
-那么，你决定要怎么做？ -我接受了。
- So,what are you gonna do? - Well,I took it!
这太好了。你会留在纽约。
That's great! So you're staying in New York!
-你高兴吗？ -是的。报酬很优厚
- You're excited,right? - You know.. Look,the money's great.
-是理所当然的选择。 -对呀。
- It's certainly the easier choice. - Right.
我本来是盼望着去巴黎的，
But,you know,I mean,was I looking forward to going to Paris? Sure.
为能在世界时装之都工作而感到兴奋。
Was I excited about working in the fashion capital of the world?
哦，太棒了。
Oh,absolutely.
不过
Yeah,but you know,this is..
这样也不错。重新回到原来的工作
It's fine. I'm fine going back to a job where I've pretty much..
我觉得还不错。 尽管我已经忘掉它了。
gotten everything out of it that I possibly can.
我不知道
I had no idea..
我不知道你为巴黎如此着迷。
I had no idea you were so excited about Paris.
你说过你感到害怕。
I mean,you said you were scared.
我想这是良性的害怕。
I mean,it was "good" scared,though,you know?
当我搬来纽约时，我感到害怕。
I mean,like "when I moved to New York" scared.
当我发现怀上艾玛时，我感到害怕。
Or "when I found out I was gonna have Emma" scared.
这很不错啦，能行的。
But this is fine. This is gonna be good.
你应该去。
You should go.
什么？
What?
那是你希望做的，去吧。
It's what you want. You should go.
你真的这么认为吗？
You really think so?
真的。
I really do.
可是我已经答应了回去。
But I already told Zelner that I would come back.
我相信他会理解的。
I'm sure he'll understand.
好的。我就这么定了。 我要去巴黎。
All right. All right! I'm gonna do it! I'm gonna go to Paris!
- 好啊 -好啊
- Yeah. - Yeah.
好啊，我要去巴黎。
I'm going to Paris!
-谢谢你，罗斯 -是啊
- Thank you,Ross. - Yeah,yeah.
我太高兴了。
Oh,I'm so happy.
我也高兴。
Then I'm happy too.
谢谢你们的到来。
Thank you all for coming.
我们相聚在此怀念一位优秀的经纪人
We're here today to pay our respects to a wonderful agent..
一位美丽的女性，…
and a beautiful woman.
内在美。
Inside.
作为艾斯黛仅有的两位客户 我们有话要说。
As Estelle's only two clients,we would like to say a few words.
我的讲稿上哪去了？
Dude,where's my speech?
这是娱乐环节 各位，这是艾尔
That is entertaining. Al Zebooker,everybody!